It's great to have a therapist and have the relationship of being able to talk things through, think things through, strategize, emotionally dump, and just like, and that's it.
And you leave there feeling lighter.
Now, therapy, I inspire my dad to go to therapy.
That's why I brought this up.
I was about to talk about, I got my mom to go.
You know what I'm saying?
My dad from Moreau, Louisiana, who-
You got your dad to go.
I got my dad to go, who that wasn't even a part of his consciousness.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah.
He would get his ass beat for being on the wrong side of the train tracks down there.
You know what I'm talking about?
My dad's 70 years old, so he grew up in them segregated and then real times where it was really bad in a place that's like even further, at that time was even further set back.